{
	"questions_and_answers": [
		{
			"question": "Do NMAMIT have their own bank and post office?",
			"answer": "Yes, they do have their own bank and post office. For further details visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/commercial-units.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "Does NMAMIT have a canteen inside the campus?",
			"answer": "Yes, NMAMIT have a canteen named Sri Durga Cafeteria and Kitchen Bells. For further details visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/canteen.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "How many seminar halls are available in our college?",
			"answer": "There are 6 seminar halls available in our college: Sadananda Open Air Auditorium, Sambhram Auditorium, Shambhavi Auditorium, Sowparnika Seminar Hall, Phalguni Seminar Hall, MCA Seminar Hall. For further details visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/auditorium.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "Where is Sadananda Open Air Auditorium located on campus?",
			"answer": "Sadananda Open Air Auditorium is located behind Dr. NSAM First Grade College Building. For further details visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/auditorium.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "Where is Sambhram Auditorium located on campus?",
			"answer": "Sambhram Auditorium is located in the basement of the Main Building. For further details visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/auditorium.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "Where is Shambhavi Auditorium located on campus?",
			"answer": "Shambhavi Auditorium is located on the 1st Floor, Administrative Block. For further details visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/auditorium.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "Where is Sowparnika Seminar Hall located on campus?",
			"answer": "Sowparnika Seminar Hall is located on the 1st Floor, Main Building. For further details visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/auditorium.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "Where is Phalguni Seminar Hall located on campus?",
			"answer": "Phalguni Seminar Hall is located on the 2nd Floor, Main Building. For further details visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/auditorium.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "Where is MCA Seminar Hall located on campus?",
			"answer": "MCA Seminar Hall is located on the 4th Floor, MCA Department, Main Building. For further details visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/auditorium.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "Is there a stationery shop located inside the campus?",
			"answer": "NET INSITITUTE is the stationery shop located inside the campus. They distribute course material at competitive prices, which includes books, record books, uniform material, etc."
		},
		{
			"question": "What facilities are provided by the central library of NMAMIT?",
			"answer": "The facilities provided by the central library include literary club activities, Library awareness Quiz, Question Paper Archives, New arrivals service. For further details visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/library.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "What are the operating hours of the central library?",
			"answer": "The central library is open from 8:00 AM to 11:00 PM."
		},
		{
			"question": "What facilities are available in the guest house for parents and guardians of students visiting the college?",
			"answer": "The guest house offers furnished rooms equipped with amenities such as AC, cot, wardrobe, telephone, TV, and internet connection in each room."
		},
		{
			"question": "Who can make bookings for the guest house?",
			"answer": "Bookings for the guest house must be made by the student at least 3 days before the arrival of their parents or guardians."
		},
		{
			"question": "Who else is accommodated in the guest house apart from parents and guardians of students?",
			"answer": "VIPs, institute guests, and invited guests are also accommodated in the guest house."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the procedure for booking a room in the guest house?",
			"answer": "Students need to make bookings for their parents or guardians at least 3 days in advance of their arrival."
		},
		{
			"question": "Is there any charge for staying in the guest house?",
			"answer": "Yes, there is a nominal rent charged for staying in the guest house."
		},
		{
			"question": "Who is the contact person for inquiries or bookings at the Guest House in Nitte?",
			"answer": "The contact person is Mr. Jagannath Shetty."
		},
		{
			"question": "How can individuals make inquiries or bookings at the Guest House in Nitte?",
			"answer": "Individuals can make bookings via phone at 08258-281288 or 08258-281388."
		},
		{
			"question": "Who should one contact for any queries related to the Guest House in Nitte?",
			"answer": "For any inquiries or bookings regarding the Guest House in Nitte, individuals should contact Mr. Jagannath Shetty, the Manager."
		},
		{
			"question": "How are student representatives selected for each class within the college?",
			"answer": "Student representatives for each class are elected by the students within that class."
		},
		{
			"question": "What are the responsibilities of the student representatives?",
			"answer": "The student representatives coordinate all academic activities and ensure the provision of necessary facilities for their respective classes."
		},
		{
			"question": "How are active student members selected for the core group responsible for organizing campus activities?",
			"answer": "Students are selected by their peers to be part of the core group responsible for organizing all activities on campus, including co-curricular and extracurricular activities."
		},
		{
			"question": "Who provides guidance to the core group of students in organizing campus activities?",
			"answer": "The core group of students receives guidance from faculty members, and their activities are mentored and monitored under the advice of the Dean of Student Welfare."
		},
		{
			"question": "How is the funding for events organized by the core group obtained?",
			"answer": "The required funding for the conduct of events is provided by the college management."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the name of sports complex at NMAMIT, Nitte?",
			"answer": "The name of the sports complex at NMAMIT, Nitte is BC Alva Sports Complex."
		},
		{
			"question": "Do NMAMIT have their own sports grounds?",
			"answer": "Yes, NMAMIT has separate Cricket ground, football ground, and a Hockey ground with a 400-meter track."
		},
		{
			"question": "When does the B.C Alva ground open?",
			"answer": "The B.C Alva ground opens at 3:30 P.M."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the mock online aptitude and technical skill tests conducted by the department of placement?",
			"answer": "The purpose of these tests is to provide pre-final year students with hands-on experience in attempting online aptitude and technical rounds, similar to those conducted by companies during campus placements."
		},
		{
			"question": "What subjects are covered in these mock tests?",
			"answer": "The mock tests cover quantitative aptitude, logical reasoning, language skills, and coding."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the name of the online testing portal created by the students?",
			"answer": "The online testing portal created by the students is called Nitte Lakshya."
		}
	]
}
